Okay, um, oh, how about Crash?
Howard "Crash" Wolowitz.
Terrific. The astronauts would love hurtling
through space with a guy named Crash.
All right, uh, how about?...
Oh, how about Rocket Man?
(Leonard:)That's not bad.
Howard "Rocket Man" Wolowitz.
(Howard:)It's great, but I told you,
I don't get to pick my nickname.
(Howard:)It has to come from the other astronauts.
(Raj:)Maybe there's a way
to get them to come up with it.
(Howard:)Like how?
(Leonard:)Once I tried carrying around
a Duncan yo-yo...
(Leonard:)...hoping the other kids
would start calling me Duncan.
- Did it work?
- No, they ended up calling me Sock Mouth...
(Leonard:)...because they took away my yo-yo
and stuffed their socks in my mouth.
(Raj:)Okay. Uh, what if we make
"Rocket Man" your ringtone...
(Raj:)...and the next time you talk to those guys,
I'll call you and they'll hear it.
That's not a terrible plan.
(Raj:)They don't call me
Brown Dynamite for nothing.